

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

- Flat No.603,Chowhan Residency,Undri,Pune,412308
- shrideshmukh1001@gmail.com
- +91-9689796002/8999505299
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/shrishailya-deshmukh/
- https://shrideshmukh.github.io

## SKILLS SUMMARY

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- JQuery
- SASS
- BootstrapStudio
- Adobe Photoshop
- Invision Studio
- Adobe XD

# SHRISHAILYA DESHMUKH

# **SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

### **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Software Engineer Specialist with 6 years of experience in the management of the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery. Skilled with Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD and web design technologies (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap).

## **ROLES & RESPONSIBILITIES**

- Conduct testing of completed applications, websites, and software to assess user experience
- Create, improve and use wireframes, prototypes, style guides, user flows, and effectively communicate your interaction ideas using any of these methods.
- Continually keep me and my design team updated with the latest changes in our industry's standards.
- Create Web-related design like Website theme, Web Application Design, Mobile App UI design, Wireframe Design, Prototype Design
- Convert PSD to HTML Web pages
- Create static and dynamic web pages
- Created interactive designs for complex web applications by way of page/user flow diagrams, site maps, and interactive wireframes.
- Consult with tech startups to review current products and provide design solutions to solve user needs and business challenges through user research, visual design, and prototyping

### **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION**

- Bachelor Of Computer Science and Engineering from BMIT, Solapur 2015
- Completed Diploma in Computer Science from Collage of engineering, Pandharpur 2011
- Completed 10th From Sangola Vidyamandir, Sangola in 2008

#### PERSONAL INFO

**Permeant Address** - At/post-Mahud, Tal-Sangola Dist-Solapur

Gender- Male

Marital Status - Married

**Date of Birth**- 01/04/1993

Passport No - L8313036

#### **Hobbies -**

Travelling, Reading, playing Cricket

### Language's known -

English,

Hindi,

Marathi.

### **CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES**

- Software Testing Course From Seed Infotech, Pune.
- HTML5 From SoloLearn.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Senior Software Engineer**

Xoriant Solutions Pvt Ltd | Jul 2021 - Present

- As a Senior Software engineer I have to create a web pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and new version of bootstrap.
- I have to Maintain almost 200+ sites and if needed develop customers site as per the requirement.

## **UI Developer**

Terse Software Pvt Ltd | Nov 2018 - Jul 2021

- Gathering and evaluating user requirement in collaboration with the project manager
- Presenting UI design concepts to the project stakeholders for review and feedback.
- Driving the development and communication of clear design guidelines, pattern, Libraries.
- Working closely with the development team to implement the vision.
- Re-designing UI for Android, iOS.

## **UI Developer**

Arinjay Trading Pvt Ltd | Feb 2018 - Nov 2018

- Gathering and evaluating user requirement in collaboration with the project manager
- Presenting UI design concepts to the project stakeholders for review and feedback.

## **UI/UX Designer**

Ideasailor Technolgies Pvt Ltd | Jun 2016 - Feb 2018

- Work independently and collaboratively with team members to develop UI/UX workflow and design.
- Provide QA & feedback to developers.
- Create an effective design using frontend technologies as well as tools and Re-designing UI for Android, IOS.